get4x.com 2019-06-29

# Privacy Policy - Get4x

#### Read and review the Get4x Privacy Policy

### Get4x Privacy Policy

Concerned about how your personal data is being collected and used on our site and mobile applications?

We are too.

We understand that your personally identifying information is important to you and we hope this privacy policy will assuage these concerns when using Get4x.

Get4x is a community platform that puts travellers and money changers in touch, to the mutual benefit of both parties. In the process, some user data will be collected and so this privacy policy outlines the way we collect, use and protect your personal information.

At 4xLabs, our mission is to bring about greater price transparency in the cash exchange industry, and so it makes sense that we are transparent when it comes to the type of data we collect from you and what we do with it. Do review our privacy policy below for more details, and if you have any questions, please do not hesitate to reach out to us at [feedback@get4x.com](http://get4x.com/en/feedback).

* * *

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this Get4x Site and Mobile Applications. Please read this privacy policy before using the Site and Mobile Applications or submitting any personal information. By using the Site or Mobile Applications, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the Site or Mobile Applications to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for the Get4x Site and Mobile Applications only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

**Collection of Information.** We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used only to help fulfill your specific request and improve your user experience. 

**Cookie/Tracking Technology.** The Site and Mobile Applications may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site and mobile applications, and understanding how visitors use the Site and Mobile Applications. Cookies can also help customize the Site and Mobile Applications for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

**Distribution of Information.** We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: 

  1. permitted or required by law; or,
  2. trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, 
  3. investigating fraud which has already taken place.

The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. 

**Commitment to Data Security.** Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this Site and Mobile Applications allow you to opt out of further mailings.

**Privacy Contact Information.** If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.  
Email: [feedback@get4x.com](mailto:feedback@get4x.com)  
Address: 4xLabs Pte Ltd , 37A HongKong Street, Singapore 059676

**Legal Jurisdiction.** All matters related to the site and mobile applications will be governed by the laws of Singapore, without regard to conflicts of laws provisions. You therefore agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of Singapore Courts.

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
